[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the names of the two eccentric women who lived at the estate known as Grey Gardens?", "correct_answer": "Edith and Edie Beale", "incorrect_answers": ["Elizabeth and Victoria Vanderbilt", "Natalia and Anna Carlisle", "Beatrice and Josephine Rockerfeller"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following Spanish cities is prominently mentioned in Woody Allens 2008 film Vicky Cristina Barcelona, starring Pen\u00e9lope Cruz and Javier Bardem?", "correct_answer": "Oviedo", "incorrect_answers": ["Valencia", "Seville", "Malaga"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of chocolate contains the most  flavonoids and may help lower your cholesterol?", "correct_answer": "Dark chocolate", "incorrect_answers": ["Chocolate with almonds", "Milk chocolate", "White chocolate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word means a practitioner of the martial art of Okinawan origin, karate?", "correct_answer": "Karateka", "incorrect_answers": ["Konyico", "Sojin", "Samurai"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hyenas are only found in Africa.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Baby frogs are called pups.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sancho Panza was the squire to and the best friend of Don Quixote. What does panza\u201d mean in Spanish?", "correct_answer": "Belly", "incorrect_answers": ["Fool", "Jester", "Compatriot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Giraffes were once thought to be a cross between a camel and a leopard.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress said on the stage of the 81st Academy Awards ceremony in 2009, Has anybody ever fainted here? Because I might be the first one?", "correct_answer": "Penelope Cruz", "incorrect_answers": ["Scarlett Johansson", "Natalie Portman", "Rebecca Hall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Star Wars character Darth Sidious was an apprentice of this Sith Lord.", "correct_answer": "Darth Plagueis", "incorrect_answers": ["Darth Zanarkin", "Darth Shalalagamagataga", "Darth Maul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The highest mountain in the world is named after Sir George Everest, a famous Welshman. What was his profession?", "correct_answer": "Surveyor and geographer", "incorrect_answers": ["Defender of human rights", "Actor", "President"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of anatomical structures does the Circle of Willis consist of?", "correct_answer": "Arteries", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Veins", "Neurons"]}]